Morning baths are the best, mm-yup!
No doubt!
I wonder why it feels so much
better in the morning...
That boy named Raion...
Are you sure he's no worry?
He made an agreement through
the Negotiation Right. It'll be fine.
You just have to trust Haruto.
I almost forgot how strong
her love of family was.
Her whole demeanor changes
when it comes to them.
Setting aside Raion...
May I suggest that we get Iruga and
Fukami to finally display an act of loyalty?
I suppose...
We might as well kill
two birds with one stone.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
We're home. The Queen's waiting for us.
Okay.
Move.
Don't mind Fukami. He's always like that.
So he's Yohei Fukami...
Sorry!
My stomach's acting up.
Let me go to the bathroom!
Don't shit yourself!
Three more minutes!
1. Tokyo
2. Chiba
3. Kanagawa
4. Saitama
All ready over here, for real!
All ready...
Expose the enemy's quarters?!
Yeah, using the Presentation Right.
Gobo and I have already confirmed that we
can use the Presentation Right through text
even within areas hidden
with the Concealment Right.
Wow, when did you guys do that?
To fool your enemies, you must
first fool your allies, you know?
I don't think that phrase
applies in this situation...
So, how do we locate their headquarters?
With a function of the Presentation Right...
Gobo can designate where and what
screen his messages are displayed on.
So he'll activate the
Presentation Right at 12 o'clock
and display messages in different
prefectures by the second.
A message in Tokyo at 12:00:01,
Chiba at 12:00:02,
Tokyo
Chiba
Kanagawa at 12:00:03,
and in Saitama at 12:00:04.
Kanagawa
Saitama
The messages will be displayed on this device.
It's an old model, so there are
hardly any left in the country.
I see...
The number displayed on that device
will signify which prefecture Ouno's in.
Tokyo... Chiba... Kanagawa... Saitama...
(For Real!)
12:00:04... We're in Saitama!
Almost 12:01!
On to the next step, Gobo!
I gotcha, for real!
To narrow it down even further...
Beginning at 12:01,
we'll use the same method
to display messages in cities
in population order...
1st place: Saitama
2nd place: Kawaguchi
3rd place: Kawagoe
4th place: Tokorozawa
5th place: Koshigaya
6th place: Soka
7th place: Kasukabe
Where does this place rank
in Saitama's population?
(Mm-yup!)
Second place!
Kawaguchi, Saitama
Kawaguchi City!
Jeez, man. You sure you're okay?
Yeah, my bad.
Raion... Do you mind
if I gave you a command?
Of course not! Your wish is my command!
Tonight...
Bring me Hayato Souma, the man
with the Materialization Right.
How could I be so stupid?
The Queen didn't know anything
about our team structure,
which is why I thought I could play dumb.
No, it was supposed to work...
...if this guy didn't sell us out!
I'll decide on your rank after this task.
Understood! I won't let you down!
So, you were right.
The owner of the
Materialization Right was Souma.
You pass.
Great! I guess that proves my loyalty.
Easy-peasy!
But I dunno if this church
would suit that baldy macho!
Damn it...
He's describing his appearance on purpose!
By the way, where's Yohei?
I've been looking for him.
He's gone out to prove his loyalty to me.
Speaking of loyalty!
Does Seraphiel-san need
to prove his loyalty too?
I dunno how things work around here
since I'm a newbie!
Iruga!
It's quite all right.
I've had a long relationship
with Kisaragi-san.
I'm this church's priest, and
I've promised her I would bless her
when she achieves her goal. That's all.
There ya go.
Did he just do that for me?
What's this guy up to?
Then no worries!
Well, I'm off!
Raion!
You still have time, right?
Let's battle it out with Kai!
S-Sure...
Well?
Did you get what I was talking about?
So that's really all the information
we need to beat Lady Kisaragi?
Of course!
Hey...
Couldn't you beat them yourself
right this second, if you wanted to?
Yeah, I could. Probably...
Then why?
Because "probably" isn't enough!
It has to be "definitely"!
Besides, Kai Kasai works for the Emperor,
and the Emperor sides with the Queen, right?
So that negates that scenario.
Don't tell me you think
killing them is the end of it.
Wrong! That would be incorrect!
That'll only lead to a bad ending.
Hand over Souma?!
Yeah...
Screw that! No way!
Hand him over to the Queen and Emperor?!
Absolutely not!
Let's stay calm...
Given his situation, there was
no way he could refuse.
The Queen only wants his
Materialization Right.
Instead of killing him, I'll try to convince
her to keep him alive and use him.
That way, we can avoid
the worst-case scenario.
How?
I'll explain that without Souma's stamina,
his powers can only be used once a day.
That should be reason enough
to keep him around.
But there's no guarantee that'll work!
Ouno.
Hirayama said he'd let Hikari Ebina escape
once they've gathered
enough information, right?
Yeah.
Then let's send Souma in as a spy
to help out with their escape.
We can use the solar panels here
to generate enough power for necessities.
I'll cover food and resources
with my Obtainment Right.
Ebina's information will likely be
the final piece to the puzzle...
Let's go out on a limb and make a move.
I'll come with you and Souma
when you meet up with them.
Hang on, Souma could be targeted
before we even get there.
It's too dangerous!
Which is exactly why I should be there.
Raion and Souma are both
putting their lives on the line.
You could at least let me
tag along halfway there.
We're all clear.
Head straight.
The Emperor is waiting for you.
Okay Rika, you can head back.
Confirming Raion and Souma's
teleportation with the Emperor.
Raion, take him down
to the warehouse, will ya?
I'll go get the Queen.
Warehouse?
Not the church?
She said the warehouse is fine since
it's not like he's joining our team.
I'll explain why later, so could you
tell her not to kill him right away?
Okay!
This kid's... the Emperor...
All right, heading back to the base.
Roger that.
Rika! Look out!
A man came out of the building behind you!
What?
Who the hell are you?
Large earrings...
Punk chick with a prosthetic...
You must be the chick
who blocks all physical attacks.
Is he the Queen's servant?
I can't make a run for it with my leg.
I gotta find a way to turn him back...
I need a bit more time. And for that...
I gotta show them my loyalty somehow.
Huh? What're you talking about?
I know it's wrong to do this!
Curse me if you have to.
Transfer!
W-What the hell...?
Rika!
I'm nothing but a cowardly, weak man.
But before I go to hell, there's
one thing I need to settle.
With your sacrifice and in return
for my sins, I'll kill the Queen.
Omi...
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
I see...
If taking his Right will limit its usage,
I suppose we're better off
keeping him to do the work for us.
I've already put him in his place.
I'm happy to hear that.
Wow, he's done a great job of
gaining the Queen's trust...
Take him to the dungeon.
Have Seraphiel stand guard.
As you wish.
Then perhaps I'll have you start
with materializing some resources.
Good work today.
You may go back.
I'm off then. Take care.
I'll watch out for the Negotiation Right and
if anything happens, I'll have them get you.
Don't worry.
Raion!
See ya tomorrow!
Yeah.
I've gotta be even more on guard
from now on...
Rika... died?
It happened so quick...
If only I didn't take her with us.
Suzuki volunteered to go with you two.
Lamenting over her death won't help us.
We have to reassess and plan countermeasures.
Don't you see our friend just died?!
How could you say that?!
Time won't wait for all of us
to wallow in despair.
They have every right to mourn.
I've decided to leave my grief with them.
In turn, I'll act as the voice of reason.
That's what friends are for.
To sum up Shinozaki Sensei and Raion-kun's
stories, the culprit must be Yohei Fukami.
The moment he said "transfer",
his injury moved from him to Rika.
Given that Rika's Evasion Right didn't
work, it must be a Prime Right
under the Permission Attribute...
...one of the strongest among them, at that.
Transfer Right
Likely something akin
to the Transfer Right...
Evasion Right
One concern is that Rika's
death possibly resulted
Evasion Right
in the Queen's obtainment
of the Evasion Right.
Isn't that like... really bad?
For now, we can only focus on fully
supporting Raion-kun's infiltration.
How's Omi?
We've just gotta let him be for a while.
No matter what...
Let's win, no matter what!
Let's do it!
Raion!
I won't let anyone else die!
Phew...
Sorry about the daily trips day and night.
Don't sweat it!
We're in this together, Haruto!
Haruto?!
Yeah, totally!
Haruto... that's me!
I can't believe this is the same
person as that Emperor...
No! I can't let my emotions get to me!
Only my sister calls me that.
I gotta do my part if we want to win...
You're making me blush!
Now that we've taken down another enemy,
we can focus on the real task at hand!
Real task?
Wait, I haven't told you yet?
The main objective for Sis
is to find someone.
Oh, we're looking for someone?
Cool, can I do anything to help?
Really? Sure!
So who are we looking for?
It's—
Welcome back, Emperor.
Thanks, Seraphiel.
Perfect timing, Raion-kun.
Me?
You see, it's about Souma-san...
He's been asking for you all day,
and I'm honestly at a bit of a loss.
I couldn't keep quiet anymore,
but at least this place has some "light."
I wish I could send some over
to that dim headquarters.
Fine then, I'll do that for you.
Like I'd trust you!
Tell Yagihashi to come get it!
I can't waste my time
listening to your bickering.
Poor thing, being betrayed like this...
You're one to talk!
You got this, Raion.
I see...
"Light" in Japanese is "Hikari"...
he's talking about Ebina.
He's talking in simple code.
"Come get Hikari."
It was a little awkward, but
I don't think Seraphiel noticed.
Gobo, did you get any of that?
Not at all, for real.
Glad it only took half a day
since they got Souma!
So how will we help Hikari escape?
All we know is that they're
somewhere in Kawaguchi, Saitama.
That's not an issue.
Gobo, could you display a map?
Whenever we use Meguru's Exchange Right,
we have to pass through midway points
because of distance limits.
I've memorized some distinctive
scenery from those locations.
Tokyo
Saitama
We transport with the
Exchange Right in this order.
The Exchange Right can't transport very far,
and we transported a few times after the
last midway point to reach their headquarters.
Which means their location
is somewhere around here.
That narrows it down.
As long as we're close,
it's only a matter of time before
we break the concealed barrier.
We just need to get close enough
so we can use the Visualization Right
to find their headquarters.
Of course!
It's the same as our first battle.
As long as we're in the area...
But that means sending Shinozaki
to the front line with us...
I can't lie. It'll be dangerous.
It's the only way.
I accept the risks.
Yagihashi and Omi need to
stay here to protect our base.
Which leaves...
Right, I figured.
As soon as we enter the concealed area,
Shinozaki will confirm
visual of their headquarters.
Then Ryuta will go in by himself
to help Souma and Hikari escape.
It'll be dangerous, but it's our best shot.
Let's do it to win!
You're late! What were you doing, Raion?
S-Sorry... My stomach hurts real bad...
You have such a sensitive stomach!
Sorry, I gotta use the bathroom...
First, I'll keep Haruto and them here...
By that time...
Souma's guard should be changing to Hikari.
I found it!
Take the path to your right
and head straight for 200 meters!
Roger that!
Pass through the bushes on the right!
'Kay!
Fuse!
Separate!
I can hold them for 20 minutes tops...
Get out before we come back!
Sorry for the wait!
Fuse!
Separate!
I don't remember you being this strong...
Ready? Let's meet up with Shinozaki Sensei.
Shinozaki-san's here too?!
Sensei! I've got both of them!
Heading over now!
Roger that! Good work!
I don't see any enemies yet.
Now's my chance to...
Dust explosion?!
I'm under attack at Point A!
Change meeting to Point B!
Under attack?!
Ask Raion-kun to send help!
Damn it! There's no service!
Souma?!
My body's giving out...
I don't have much strength left.
That must have been...
Kou of the Three Powers!
I need to find a way to escape!
What could his Prime Right be?!
Shinozaki here...
I won't be able to meet up.
Sensei?!
Find a way back, no matter what!
I'm wishing you guys success!
Damn it!
He can't be...
Forget meeting up.
We're heading back now!
But how?!
The same way Knight escaped...
Fuse!
Did it work?!
It'll take at least a few seconds
to run from that...
I'll keep his hands full!
Take Hikari back while you can!
Don't be stupid!
You barely have any strength left!
Requesting escape!
Prime Right of Materialization!
Materialize all cards at once!!
They got away.
Sorry Eren...
Even Shinozaki-san put his life on the line.
I gotta do my part and follow suit.
Go win it... you guys.
Loyalty